Guide to the Robert A. M. Stern Architects Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Project records for 1985-1986, 1983-2004; Accession 2012-M-058
  - Milwin Farm (Ocean Township, NJ) (85093), 1985 - 1986
    - Project Drawings
      - House 5 - Working Drawings for Unspecified Lot (Box 80)
      - House 6 - Working Drawings for Block 60.2, Lot 14 (Box 80)
      - Landscape Architect (Box 80)
      - Lerner Residence - Preliminary Working Drawings for Block 60.2, Lot 11 (Box 80)
      - Lerner Residence - Working Drawings for Block 60.2, Lot 11 (Box 81)
      - Lot Layout Studies (Box 81)
      - Minder Poolhouse (Box 81)
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 81)
      - Site Surveys (Box 81)
      - Small Drawings (Box 16, Folder 343)
      - Small-Scale Design Drawings (Box 139, Folder 93)
    - Project Sketches
      - Sketches - Elevations, Floor Plans (Box 139, Folder 91)
      - Sketches - Lot Layout Studies (Box 139, Folder 92)
  - Addition to the Sheldon Memorial Library, St. Paul's School (Concord, NH) (85094), 1985 - 1986
    See Also: 87014 - St. Paul's School Library.
    - Project File (Box 16, Folder 350)
    - Project Images (Box 40, Folder 53)
    - Project Drawings
      - Existing Conditions (Box 82)
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 82)
      - Progress Prints (Box 82)
    - Project Sketches (Box 139, Folder 94)
  - Milwin Farm: Estate House Renovation (Ocean Township, NJ) (85095), 1985 - 1988
    See Also: 85093 - Milwin Farm Houses 85096 - Milwin Farm: Wishnick House 86018 - Milwin Farm: Gatehouse and Poolhouse 86078 - Milwin Farm: Tennis Pavilion.
    - Project File (Box 16, Folder 351)
    - Project Images (Box 40, Folder 54)
    - Project Drawings
      - Existing Conditions (Box 82)
      - Landscape Architect (Box 82)
      - Working Drawings (Box 82)
      - Working Drawings - Lass Garage Addition (Box 82)
    - Project Sketches - Lass Garage Addition (Box 140, Folder 95)
  - Milwin Farm: Wishnick House (Ocean Township, NJ) (85096), 1985 - 1986
    - Project File (Box 16, Folder 352)
    - Project Images (Box 40, Folder 55)
    - Project Drawings
      - Design Drawings (Box 83)
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 83)
      - Working Drawings (Box 83)
    - Project Sketches (Box 140, Folder 96)
  - Meadowbrook II (Hempstead, NY) (85097), 1986 - 1989
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 16, Folder 353)
      - Authorities (Box 16, Folder 354)
      - Landscape (Box 16, Folder 355)
      - Memoranda (Box 16, Folder 356)
      - Notes (Box 16, Folder 357)
      - Prices (Box 16, Folder 358)
      - Site Information (Box 16, Folder 359)
      - Site Plan/Survey (Box 16, Folder 360)
    - Project Images (Box 40, Folder 56)
    - Project Drawings
      - Design Drawings (Box 83)
      - Presentation Drawings - Mylar (Box 83)
      - Presentation Drawings - Vellum (Box 83)
    - Project Sketches
      - Sketches - Elevations, Floor Plans (Box 140, Folder 97)
      - Sketches - Site Plans (Box 140, Folder 98)
  - The Shops at Somerset Square (Glastonbury, CT) (86001), 1986 - 1988
    See Also: 86034 - Glastonbury Housing 88020 - Somerset Square Office Condominium 93009 -- Glastonbury Alterations A04003 - Somerset Square Alterations.
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 17, Folder 361)
      - Architect/Consultant (Box 17, Folder 362)
      - Architect/Contractor (Box 17, Folder 363)
      - Authorities (Box 17, Folder 364)
      - Geotechnical (Box 17, Folder 365)
      - Lighting (Box 17, Folder 366)
      - Marketing Center (Box 17, Folder 367)
      - Mechanical Design/Build Engineer (Box 17, Folder 368)
      - Mechanical/Electrical Engineer (Box 17, Folder 369)
      - Memoranda (Box 17, Folder 370)
      - Notes (Box 17, Folder 371)
      - Project Manual - Construction Package One (Box 17, Folder 372)
      - Project Manual - Construction Package Two (Box 17, Folder 373)
      - Publicity (Box 17, Folder 374)
      - Signage (Box 18, Folder 376)
      - Site Information (Box 18, Folder 377)
      - Specifications - Bid Package 2 (Box 18, Folder 379)
      - Specifications - Bid Package 3 (Box 18, Folder 380)
      - Structural (Box 18, Folder 381)
    - Project Images (1) (Box 40, Folder 57)
    - Project Images (2) (Box 40, Folder 58)
    - Project Drawings
      - Construction Package One (Box 84)
      - Design Drawings (Box 84)
      - Final Development Plan - Phase 3 (Box 84)
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 84)
      - Shrink Set (Box 18, Folder 375)
      - Small Drawings (Box 18, Folder 378)
      - Working Drawings (Box 85)
  - LaJolla Townhouses (LaJolla, CA) (86002), Project File, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 382)
  - Grand Harbor, Harbor Center (Vero Beach, FL) (86003), 1986 - 1988
    See Also: 86004, 86005, 86006, 86007, 86035, 86050, 86051.
    - Project File
      - Architect/Consultant (Box 18, Folder 383)
      - Authorities (Box 18, Folder 384)
      - Civil (Box 18, Folder 385)
      - Harbor Master's Building (Box 18, Folder 386)
      - Lighting (Box 18, Folder 387)
      - Marina (Box 18, Folder 388)
      - Mechanical (Box 18, Folder 389)
      - Memoranda (Box 18, Folder 390)
      - Notes (Box 18, Folder 391)
      - Parking (Box 18, Folder 392)
      - Project Manual (Box 19, Folder 393)
      - Real Estate Advisor (Box 19, Folder 394)
      - Site Information (Box 19, Folder 395)
      - Specifications (Box 19, Folder 398)
    - Project Images (Box 40, Folder 59)
    - Project Drawings
      - Civil Engineer (Box 85)
      - Preliminary Pricing Set (Box 86)
      - Presentation Drawings - Mylar (Box 86)
      - Presentation Drawings - Prints (Box 86)
      - Presentation Drawings - Vellum (Box 86)
      - Sketch Drawings (Box 87)
      - Small Drawings - Apartment Types (Box 19, Folder 396)
      - Small Drawings - General (Box 19, Folder 397)
      - Working Drawings - Buildings B through G (Box 87)
      - Working Drawings - Buildings H through L (Box 88)
    - Project Sketches (Box 141, Folder 99)
  - Grand Harbor, Golf Club (Vero Beach, FL) (86004), 1986 - 1988
    See Also: 86003, 86005, 86006, 86007, 86035, 86050, 86051.
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 19, Folder 399)
      - Authorities (Box 19, Folder 400)
      - Club Consultant (Box 19, Folder 401)
      - Lighting (Box 19, Folder 402)
      - Memoranda (Box 19, Folder 403)
      - Prices (Box 19, Folder 404)
      - Project Manual (Box 19, Folder 405)
      - Site Information (Box 19, Folder 406)
      - Specifications (Box 19, Folder 408)
    - Project Images (Box 40, Folder 60)
    - Project Drawings
      - Civil Engineer (Box 88)
      - Preliminary Pricing Set (Box 88)
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 89)
      - Record Set (Box 89)
      - Small Drawings (Box 19, Folder 407)
      - Small-Scale Design Development Drawings (Box 141, Folder 101)
      - Working Drawings (Box 89)
    - Project Sketches (Box 141, Folder 100)
  - Grand Harbor, Tennis Club (Vero Beach, FL) (86005), 1986 - 1988
    See Also: 86003, 86004, 86006, 86007, 86035, 86050, 86051.
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 19, Folder 409)
      - Electrical/Mechanical (Box 19, Folder 410)
      - Lighting (Box 19, Folder 411)
      - Memoranda (Box 19, Folder 412)
      - Prices (Box 19, Folder 413)
      - Project Manual (Box 19, Folder 414)
      - Restaurant (Box 19, Folder 415)
      - Site Information (Box 19, Folder 416)
      - Specifications (Box 20, Folder 418)
    - Project Images (Box 40, Folder 61)
    - Project Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 90)
      - Record Set (Box 90)
      - Small Drawings (Box 20, Folder 417)
      - Working Drawings (Box 90)
    - Project Sketches (Box 141, Folder 102)
  - The Courtyard Houses at Grand Harbor (Vero Beach, FL) (86006), 1986 - 1989
    See Also: 86003, 86004, 86005, 86007, 86035, 86050, 86051.
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 20, Folder 419)
      - Architect/Contractor (Box 20, Folder 420)
      - Authorities (Box 20, Folder 421)
      - Civil (Box 20, Folder 422)
      - Condominium Documents (Box 20, Folder 423)
      - Doors and Windows (Box 20, Folder 424)
      - Field Reports (Box 20, Folder 425)
      - Geotechnical (Box 20, Folder 426)
      - Landscape (Box 20, Folder 427)
      - Mechanical/Electrical (Box 20, Folder 428)
      - Memoranda (Box 20, Folder 429)
      - Notes (Box 20, Folder 430)
      - Project Manual (Box 20, Folder 431)
      - Real Estate Advisor (Box 20, Folder 432)
      - Site Information (Box 21, Folder 434)
      - Specifications (Box 21, Folder 436)
      - Structural (Box 21, Folder 437)
      - Submittal and Shop Drawing Record (Box 21, Folder 438)
    - Project Images (1) (Box 41, Folder 62)
    - Project Images (2) (Box 41, Folder 63)
    - Project Drawings
      - Civil Engineer - Land Development Plans (Box 91)
      - Civil Engineer - Site Plans (Box 91)
      - Design Drawings (Box 91)
      - Landscape Architect (Box 91)
      - MEP Engineers (Box 91)
      - Progress Prints (Box 91)
      - Record Sets (Box 92)
      - Shrink Set (Box 20, Folder 433)
      - Small Drawings (Box 21, Folder 435)
      - Small-Scale Design Drawings (Box 141, Folder 104)
      - Structural Engineer (Box 92)
      - Working Drawings (Box 93)
    - Project Sketches (Box 141, Folder 103)
  - Grand Harbor, Harbor Center Island (Vero Beach, FL) (86007), 1986 - 1988
    See Also: 86003, 86004, 86005, 86006, 86035, 86050, 86051.
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 21, Folder 439)
      - Authorities (Box 21, Folder 440)
      - Fire Protection (Box 21, Folder 441)
      - Lighting (Box 21, Folder 442)
      - Marina (Box 21, Folder 443)
      - Mechanical (Box 21, Folder 444)
      - Memoranda (Box 21, Folder 445)
      - Paver-Pedestal System (Box 21, Folder 446)
      - Prices (Box 21, Folder 447)
      - Seawall (Box 21, Folder 448)
      - Site Plan/Survey (Box 21, Folder 449)
      - Specifications (Box 21, Folder 452)
    - Project Images (Box 41, Folder 64)
    - Project Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 93)
      - Record Prints (Box 93)
      - Record Set (Box 94)
      - Sketch Drawings (Box 94)
      - Small Drawings - Apartment Types (Box 21, Folder 450)
      - Small Drawings - General (Box 21, Folder 451)
      - Working Drawings - Part 1 (Box 95)
      - Working Drawings - Part 2 (Box 95)
    - Project Sketches (Box 142, Folder 105)
  - Craftsman Farms (Parsippany, NJ) (86008), 1986 - 1987
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 22, Folder 453)
      - Architect/Consultant (Box 22, Folder 454)
      - Authorities (Box 22, Folder 455)
      - Memoranda (Box 22, Folder 456)
      - Publicity (Box 22, Folder 457)
      - Site Information (Box 22, Folder 458)
    - Project Images (Box 41, Folder 65)
    - Project Drawings
      - Civil Engineer (Box 96)
      - Landscape Consultant (Box 96)
      - Presentation Drawings - Mylar (Box 96)
      - Presentation Drawings - Vellum (Box 96)
      - Small-Scale Design Drawings (Box 142, Folder 107)
      - Working Drawings (Box 96)
    - Project Sketches (Box 142, Folder 106)
  - Jewelry for Acme (86017), 1986 - 1987
    - Project File (Box 22, Folder 459)
    - Project Images (Box 41, Folder 66)
  - Milwin Farm (Ocean Township, NJ) (86018), 1986 - 1987
    See Also: 85093 - Milwin Farm Houses 85095 - Milwin Farm: Estate House Renovation 85096 - Milwin Farm: Wishnick House 86078 - Milwin Farm: Tennis Pavilion.
    - Project Images (Box 41, Folder 67)
    - Project Drawings (Box 97)
    - Project Sketches
      - Sketches - Gatehouse (Box 142, Folder 108)
      - Sketches - Poolhouse (Box 142, Folder 109)
  - Wolfer Residence (Great Neck, NY) (86020), Project File, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 460)
  - Brooklyn Law School, 250 Joralemon Street (New York, NY) (86024), 1986 - 1990
    See Also: 90025 - Brooklyn Law School.
    This is an unbuilt project. This project number represents the first scheme/phase of a Brooklyn Law School addition. The project was eventually built, incorporating significant elements of this design, under project number 90025.
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 22, Folder 461)
      - Authorities (Box 22, Folder 462)
      - Mechanical (Box 22, Folder 463)
      - Memoranda (Box 22, Folder 464)
      - Notes (Box 22, Folder 465)
      - Pedestrian Bridge (Box 22, Folder 466)
      - Prices (Box 22, Folder 467)
      - Renovation (Box 22, Folder 468)
    - Project Images (Box 41, Folder 68)
    - Project Drawings
      - Existing Conditions (Box 142, Folder 110)
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 97)
      - Record Prints (Box 97)
      - Street Bridge (Box 97)
    - Project Sketches
      - Sketches - Elevations, Floor Plans (Box 142, Folder 111)
      - Sketches - Street Bridge (Box 142, Folder 112)
  - Residence in River Oaks (Houston, TX) (86025), 1986 - 1988
    See Also: 88035 - Residence in River Oaks.
    This is an unbuilt project. This project number represents the first scheme of a house in River Oaks. This design was not built. The records for the second scheme, which was built, can be found under project number 88035.
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 22, Folder 469)
      - Architect/Consultant (Box 22, Folder 470)
      - Civil (Box 22, Folder 471)
      - Equipment (Box 22, Folder 472)
      - Hardware (Box 22, Folder 473)
      - Interiors (Box 22, Folder 474)
      - Landscape (Box 22, Folder 475)
      - Lighting (Box 22, Folder 476)
      - Marble (Box 22, Folder 477)
      - Mechanical (Box 22, Folder 478)
      - Memoranda (Box 23, Folder 479)
      - Program Background (Box 23, Folder 480)
      - Project Manual (Box 23, Folder 481)
      - Publicity (Box 23, Folder 482)
      - Specifications (Box 23, Folder 484)
      - Structural (Box 23, Folder 485)
      - Swimming Pool (Box 23, Folder 486)
    - Project Images (Box 41, Folder 69)
    - Project Drawings
      - Lighting Consultant (Box 98)
      - Presentation Drawings - Mylar (Box 98)
      - Presentation Drawings - Vellum (Box 98)
      - Progress Prints (Box 98)
      - Record Sets (Box 99)
      - Site Surveys (Box 99)
      - Small Drawings (Box 23, Folder 483)
      - Working Drawing - Doghouse (Box 99)
      - Working Drawings - Construction Issue, Part 1 (Box 100)
      - Working Drawings - Construction Issue, Part 2 (Box 101)
      - Working Drawings - Construction Issue, Part 3 (Box 101)
      - Working Drawings - Construction Issue, Part 4 (Box 102)
      - Working Drawings - Construction Issue, Part 5 (Box 102)
      - Working Drawings - Issue to Structural and Mechanical Engineers (Box 103)
      - Working Drawings - Progress Issue (Box 103)
    - Project Sketches (Box 142, Folder 113)
  - Shapiro: East Hampton Interiors (East Hampton, NY) (86026), Project File, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 487)
    See Also: 81140 - Cove Hollow Farm Lot 13: Shapiro House 85043 -- Cove Hollow Farm, Lot 13: Shapiro House Alterations 88007 -- Shapiro House Reconstruction.
  - Addition to the Colonnade Hotel (Boston, MA) (86027), 1986
    - Project File (Box 23, Folder 488)
    - Project Images (Box 41, Folder 70)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box 103)
  - Stuart Townhouse Renovations (New York, NY) (86030), 1985 - 1986
    See Also: 81295 - Stuart Townhouse.
    - Project File (Box 23, Folder 489)
    - Project Images (Box 41, Folder 71)
    - Project Drawings
      - Small-Scale Design Drawings (Box 142, Folder 115)
      - Working Drawings (Box 103)
    - Project Sketches (Box 142, Folder 114)
  - Glastonbury Housing (Glastonbury, CT) (86034), 1986 - 1987
    - Project File (Box 23, Folder 490)
    - Project Images (Box 41, Folder 72)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box 103)
  - Grand Harbor (Vero Beach, FL) (86035), 1986 - 1989
    See Also: 86003 - Grand Harbor: Center Crescent 86004 - Grand Harbor: Golf Club 86005 - Grand Harbor: Tennis Club 86006 - Grand Harbor: Courtyard Houses 86007 - Grand Harbor: Center Island 86050 - Grand Harbor: Swim Club 86051 - Grand Harbor: Bridges.
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 23, Folder 491)
      - Architect/Consultant (Box 23, Folder 492)
      - Contracts (Box 23, Folder 493)
      - Fees (Box 23, Folder 494)
      - Maps and Directions (Box 23, Folder 495)
      - Memoranda (Box 23, Folder 496)
      - Notes (Box 23, Folder 497)
      - Project Directory (Box 24, Folder 498)
      - Publicity (Box 24, Folder 499)
      - Renderer and Model Maker (Box 24, Folder 500)
      - Schedules (Box 24, Folder 501)
      - Site Information (Box 24, Folder 502)
    - Project Images (Box 41, Folder 73)
    - Project Drawings (Box 104)
  - Mexx: Los Angeles Showroom (Los Angeles, CA) (86036), 1986
    - Project File (Box 24, Folder 503)
    - Project Images (Box 41, Folder 74)
    - Project Drawings (Box 104)
    - Project Sketches (Box 142, Folder 116)
  - Master Plan, Fine Arts Village, University of California, Irvine (Irvine, CA) (86037), 1986 - 1989
    See Also: 86072 - Fine Arts Studio IV, University of California, Irvine 88062 - Humanities Master Plan, University of California, Irvine.
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 24, Folder 504)
      - Contracts (Box 24, Folder 505)
      - Fine Arts Master Plan (Box 24, Folder 506)
      - Long Range Development Plan (Box 24, Folder 507)
      - Memoranda (Box 24, Folder 508)
      - Middle Earth Residence Halls (Box 24, Folder 509)
    - Project Images (Box 41, Folder 75)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box 104)
    - Project Sketches (Box 143, Folder 117)
  - Residence in Wassenaar (Wassenaar, Netherlands) (86038), 1986 - 1987
    - Project File (Box 24, Folder 510)
    - Project Images (Box 41, Folder 76)
    - Project Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 104)
      - Small-Scale Design Drawings (Box 143, Folder 120)
    - Project Sketches
      - Sketches - Elevations, Floor Plans, Sections (Box 143, Folder 118)
      - Sketches - Interior (Box 143, Folder 119)
  - Desert House (Phoenix, AZ) (86040), 1986
    - Project Images (Box 41, Folder 77)
    - Monograph Drawings (Box 104)
    - Project Sketches (Box 143, Folder 121)
  - Brinkley/Joel Apartment (New York, NY) (86041), Project File, 1986 - 1987 (Box 24, Folder 511)
  - Arizona Biltmore, Parcel 2 (Phoenix, AZ) (86044), 1986
    - Project File (Box 24, Folder 512)
    - Project Drawings (Box 105)
    - Project Sketches (Box 143, Folder 122)
  - Residence at Wilderness Point (Fishers Island, NY) (86045), 1986 - 1989
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 24, Folder 513)
      - Architect/Contractor (Box 24, Folder 514)
      - Architect/Decorator (Box 24, Folder 515)
      - Authorities (Box 24, Folder 516)
      - Awnings (Box 24, Folder 517)
      - Boardwalk (Box 24, Folder 518)
      - Closets (Box 24, Folder 519)
      - Contract (Box 24, Folder 520)
      - Doors and Windows (Box 25, Folder 521)
      - Equipment (Box 25, Folder 522)
      - Existing Conditions (Box 25, Folder 523)
      - Fireplace/Chimneys (Box 25, Folder 524)
      - Flower Border (Box 25, Folder 525)
      - Hardware (Box 25, Folder 526)
      - Interiors (Box 25, Folder 527)
      - Irrigation (Box 25, Folder 528)
      - Legal (Box 25, Folder 529)
      - Lighting (Box 25, Folder 530)
      - Mechanical (Box 25, Folder 531)
      - Memoranda (Box 25, Folder 532)
      - Millwork (Box 25, Folder 533)
      - Neighbors (Box 25, Folder 534)
      - Paint Schedule (Box 25, Folder 535)
      - Playground (Box 25, Folder 536)
      - Plumbing (Box 25, Folder 537)
      - Pool (Box 25, Folder 538)
      - Prices (Box 25, Folder 539)
      - Publicity (Box 25, Folder 540)
      - Punch Lists (Box 25, Folder 541)
      - Screen Planting (Box 26, Folder 542)
      - Sewage (Box 26, Folder 543)
      - Site Plan/Landscape (Box 26, Folder 544)
      - Site Plan/Survey (Box 26, Folder 545)
      - Specifications (Box 26, Folder 547)
      - Steam Generator (Box 26, Folder 548)
      - Structural (Box 26, Folder 549)
    - Project Images (1) (Box 41, Folder 78)
    - Project Images (2) (Box 41, Folder 79)
    - Project Images (3) (Box 41, Folder 80)
    - Project Images (4) (Box 41, Folder 81)
    - Project Drawings
      - Design Drawings - Architecture (Box 105)
      - Design Drawings - Landscape (Box 105)
      - Details (Box 105)
      - Presentation Drawings - Mylar (Box 106)
      - Presentation Drawings - Vellum (Box 106)
      - Progress Set (Box 106)
      - Small Drawings (Box 26, Folder 546)
      - Small-Scale Design Drawings - Mylar (Box 143, Folder 128)
      - Small-Scale Design Drawings - Vellum (Box 143, Folder 129)
      - Working Drawings (Box 106)
    - Project Sketches
      - Sketches - Landscape Design, Elevations and Sections (Box 143, Folder 123)
      - Sketches - Landscape Design, Fence Studies (Box 143, Folder 124)
      - Sketches - Landscape Design, Garden Studies (Box 143, Folder 125)
      - Sketches - Landscape Design, Pool (Box 143, Folder 126)
      - Sketches - Landscape Design, Site Plans (Box 143, Folder 127)
  - Safdeye Residence (New York, NY) (86046), 1986
    - Project File (Box 26, Folder 550)
    - Project Images (Box 41, Folder 82)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box 106)
    - Project Sketches (Box 143, Folder 130)
  - St. Andrews Phase I Completion (Hastings-on-Hudson, NY) (86048), Project File, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 551)
    See Also: 82165, 84216, 84217, 85065.
  - Grand Harbor, The Swim Club (Vero Beach, FL) (86050), 1986 - 1988
    See Also: 86003, 86004, 86005, 86006, 86007, 86035, 86051.
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 26, Folder 552)
      - Foundation Investigation (Box 26, Folder 553)
      - Fountains (Box 26, Folder 554)
      - Lighting (Box 26, Folder 555)
      - Specifications (Box 26, Folder 556)
    - Project Images (Box 42, Folder 83)
    - Project Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 107)
      - Record Set (Box 107)
      - Working Drawings (Box 107)
    - Project Sketches (Box 144, Folder 131)
  - Ettl Farm Development (Princeton, NJ) (86055), 1986 - 1987
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 26, Folder 557)
      - Authorities (Box 26, Folder 558)
      - Landscape (Box 26, Folder 559)
      - Memoranda (Box 26, Folder 560)
      - Site Plan/Survey (Box 26, Folder 561)
    - Project Images (Box 42, Folder 84)
    - Project Drawings
      - Landscape Architect (Box 108)
      - Presentation Drawings - Mylar (Box 144, Folder 132)
      - Presentation Drawings - Vellum (Box 144, Folder 133)
      - Small Drawings (Box 26, Folder 562)
    - Project Sketches
      - Sketches - 2 Family Manor House (Box 144, Folder 134)
      - Sketches - 3 Family Manor House (Box 144, Folder 135)
      - Sketches - 4 Family Manor House (Box 144, Folder 136)
      - Sketches - Site Plans (Box 144, Folder 137)
  - CBS/Hines (Stamford, CT) (86056), 1986
    - Project File (Box 26, Folder 563)
    - Small-Scale Design Drawings (Box 144, Folder 139)
    - Project Sketches (Box 144, Folder 138)
  - Mexx Retail Shop (Amsterdam, Netherlands) (86058), 1986 - 1987
    - Project File
      - Architect/Architect (Box 26, Folder 564)
      - Architect/Client (Box 26, Folder 565)
      - Architect/Consultant (Box 26, Folder 566)
      - Architect/Contractor (Box 26, Folder 567)
      - Interior Designer (Box 26, Folder 568)
      - Lighting (Box 26, Folder 569)
      - Memoranda (Box 26, Folder 570)
      - Structural (Box 26, Folder 571)
    - Project Images (Box 42, Folder 85)
    - Project Drawings
      - Monograph Drawing (Box 108)
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 108)
      - Record Sets (Box 108)
      - Working Drawings (Box 108)
    - Project Sketches
      - Sketches - Elevations, Floor Plans (Box 144, Folder 140)
      - Sketches - Interior (Box 144, Folder 141)
  - Apartment House, Fan Pier Development (Boston, MA) (86059), 1986 - 1987
    See Also: A06001 - Fan Pier A12003 - Fan Pier.
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 26, Folder 572)